[Music]
[Música]
Well family, you probably know about this
bueno familia seguramente sabéis de este
topic because it went very viral on Twitter
tema porque se hizo muy viral en twitter
tonight. What happened last night?
esta noche que ha pasado esta noche
No, the other one, okay, 6 are very viral
anterior no la otra vale 6 son muy viral
and the face here, I don't know how to
y es que la cara de aquí no sé cómo se
pronounce it, ACN soccer, Axo Serna, the face
pronuncia acn soccer axo serna la cara
of Axzo, well, it has been leaked. His face was not known, it
de axzo ser pues ha filtrado no se
was totally anonymous. His face is
conocía su cara era totalmente anónimo
not known, what it was, but of course
no se conoce su cara cuál era pero claro
with what has happened in recent
con esto que ha pasado en estos últimos
days, no matter what, there have been
días no de que sea
get-togethers with this thing about
se han hecho quedadas con esto del
Uruguay and so on, there have been get-togethers
uruguay y demás se han hecho quedadas
in contexts that he just sent me, he
en contextos que me acaba de mandar
was doing get-togethers these days with
estaba haciendo quedadas en estos días
all the YouTubers, in fact,
de todos los youtubers hecho que se
link normally meets, well, not
reúne normalmente enlace bueno no
only in the series, in all of them, more or
solamente en la serie en todos más o
less those that get together, yes, for series and
menos los que se juntan sí para series y
things and no,
cosas y no
the question would be that among so many
la cuestión sería que entre tanta
get-togethers that they have had throughout the
quedada que han hecho durante todo el
weekend
fin de semana
thanks to my interest in the country, among all
gracias a mi interés en país entre todas
the get-togethers that they have been doing
las quedadas que han ido haciendo
during the weekend, well, they have been
durante el fin de semana pues han estado
taking photos, Juan Guarnizo has gone to the
haciendo fotos juan guarnizo ha ido a
house of euros direct with euros from
a casa de euros directos con euros desde
his headquarters, yesterday there were also a few from
su sede también fueron ayer unos cuantos
YouTube among them Juan and  ari to the
de youtube entre ellos juan y ari a la
house ibai's mansion
casa la mansión de ibai
many photos were at a party
muchas fotos estuvieron en una fiesta
many things for many things between
muchas cosas para muchas cosas entre
photo and photo what has happened to
foto y foto que es lo que ha pasado por
see is normal that in the end I get hungry there
ver es normal que al final pase hambre
are so many people there well I take
son tantísima gente hay pues yo me hago
a photo for an instagram history
una foto por un historial instagram
because look boy don't even go because look I
porque mira chico ni vaya porque mira
walk down the street with lauro because look
voy por la calle con lauro porque mira
here we have sat down to eat all
aquí nos hemos sentado a comer todos
together and I knew that he perita the yak and
juntos y sabía que él perita el yak y
everything so many people no because of what
todo tanto en tanta gente no por lo que
happens is that Beijing forgot to censor the
pasa que beijing se le olvidó censura la
face of hacks or be in a tweet and no matter how
cara de hacks o ser en un tweet y por
much a
mucho que lo borrara corriendo una
person with so much repercussion deleted it running like well there is
persona con tanta repercusión como bien
already someone who saves it there is already
ya hay alguien que la guarda ya hay
someone who saves it therefore therefore [
alguien que la guarda
Music]
[Música]
the what be was leaked as he responded the
se filtró la que ser como respondió el
good one I imagine he would not get angry it is a
bueno me imagino que no se enfadaría es
next one as quickly as he could these are
una siguiente lo más rápido que pudo son
things that happen in the end it is very
cosas que pasan al final es muy
complicated not that if you want to
complicado no es que si tú quieres
maintain your anonymity like that they were not
mantener su anonimato en plan que no se
preserved that to your face because I am
preservaron que a tu cara por
not going to show of course that is what he
no voy a mostrar por supuesto
did was upload a photo
que es lo que hizo fue subir una foto a
5 minutes  with my eyes only with my
los 5 minutos con los ojos solamente con
eyes and glasses because I had faith I
los ojos y las gafas porque tenía la fe
think and the masks okay half went and
creo y las mascarillas vale medio fue y
revealed well I have improved at
revel pues yo me ha mejorado en
any moment now the face
cualquier momento ahora el face
rebel rebel revelation of face okay
rebel rebel revelación de cara vale
in a little while and talks about the subject today so
dentro de poco y habla hoy del tema así
let's listen to them I'm getting
que vamos a escucharlos me estoy
a little lost to me in these it already
perdiendo un poquito a mí en estos ya
came out before okay okay okay a thousand thanks to
salió antes vale vale vale mil gracias a
all of you who are writing I
todos los que estáis escribiendo me
would like to clarify that what happened
gustaría aclarar que sobre lo que pasó
the other day was a mistake but of
el otro día ha sido un error pero de
seconds that story of paying of course let's
segundos esa historia de pagar claro a
see these are things that happen there are people
ver son cosas que pasa que hay gente por
unfortunately saw that they shouldn't have seen it
desgracia vio que no tenía que haber
was for me to Heron Hector me to
visto iba para mí a heron héctor yo a
three friends okay there is an option
tres amigos vale hay una opción
instagram it is for best friends where
instagram es para mejores amigos donde
we are seven people literally seven
somos siete personas literal siete
people eight as it was a story do
personas ocho como era una historia
you think yes or no I
usted es que cree que sí o que no yo
think not
creo que no
listen to what I'm telling you I'm going to look at it to
fíjate lo que te digo voy a mirarlo a
see
ver
Beijing
beijing
how can I know
cómo puedo saberlo
how can I know that
cómo puedo saberlo eso
and on twitter how can I know where
y en twitter cómo puedo saberlo dónde
where it says that does
donde lo pone eso
n't have me why if not
no me tiene por qué si no
okay let's see I'm going to see
vale a ver voy a ver
now
ahora
because it comes out light green the following d
porque sale verde claro el siguiendo d
Auro comes out green to me
auro me sale verde
that because now they have it
eso porque ahora sí me tienen
clear to me this is because now  yes he has me he had
claro esto es porque ahora sí me tiene
put me in
había metido
now he doesn't have me
ahora no me tiene
for the one who strong how strong I don't
para aquel que fuerte que fuerte no
belong to those 78 people who can
pertenezco a esa 78 personas que pueden
see the face of being you
ver la cara de ser
just did me an incredible pleasure
me acabas de hacer un gusto increíble
yes yes that car does have me why does it come out
sí sí ese auto sí me tiene por qué sale
green no never
verde no nunca
when I put stories I wouldn't know no
cuando me ponga historias no sabría no
I didn't put it in with anyone and best friends
yo no metí con nadie y mejores amigos
never because they are or not his victory neither
nunca porque no sean o no su victoria ni
for nor for everyone it's barely worth it
para ni para todo el mundo apenas
okay okay
vale vale vale
then it means that now he does
entonces quiere decir que ahora sí me
have me to see but how how can I see
tiene a ver pero cómo como puedo ver
who has me or I mean for example like
quién me tiene a mí o sea por ejemplo en
somewhere that puts
plan en alguna parte que ponga todo el
everyone who has me or with who because I
mundo que me tenga o con quién porque yo
think it's very good
creo que es muy bueno
I think that when they put you in then
yo creo que cuando a ti te meten pues ya
you also have him or the neighbor
tú también lo tienes a él o al vecino
as best friends we are all on the
para mejores amigos estamos todos en el
floor in the center we are talking
piso del centro estamos hablando
a lot and for some photo when I
muchísimo y por alguna fotito cuando me
like promotion or videos administer
gusta promoción o vídeos administrar
human
humano
for a few seconds to my
durante unos segundos a mi perfil
public profile and I sincerely
público y yo sinceramente
the world falls on me at that
a mí se me cae el mundo encima en ese
moment I said that I thought there was no
momento dije que pensaba que no hay
rush it
apuro
was literally 19 seconds 20 seconds I
fueron literal 19 segundos 20 segundos
said well I don't think you know I don't think
dije yo bueno no creo que sabes no creo
many people have seen a mistake there are
que mucha gente haya visto error hay
people who are very sick  Above all I
gente que está muy enferma sobre todo yo
think that Silvera passes by another person not so many
creo que silvera pasa otra persona no
people if they saw given that it is said
tanta gente si viera dado que se cuenta
that that moment is not a story and
que ese momento no es una historia y
some visits have the second
algunas visitas tiene al segundo
to see is that of how many followers now
a ver es que de cuántos seguidores ahora
on Instagram half a million and a half something like that I
en instagram medio millón y medio algo
think I had 2
así creo que tenía 2
12% thousand the truth 6,000 you upload a
12% mil la verdad 6.000 tú subes una
story and always out of a hundred thousand people it
historia y siempre de cien mil personas
is very likely that someone asks for
es muy probable que alguien le pides
two victories
entran dos victorias
but it has happened to me there are people who
pero me ha pasado a mí hay gente que
are very sick and have seen it literally
está muy enferma y lo ha visto literal
in 19 seconds it is less than 19 seconds
en 19 segundos son menos de 19 segundos
and it came out from there I have already apologized
y salió a partir de ahí yo ya le pidió
100,000 times
100.000 veces
to the person involved in it he
disculpas a la persona implicada en ella
tells me that it is great that I should not
me dice que está genial que no me
worry about anything he has been more
preocupe por nada ha estado más
attentive to me these days than I have
pendiente de mí en estos días que yo del
sincerely let's see I'm going to stop the room
sinceramente a ver voy a parar la salita
because I can't speak and I lose the thread
porque no puedo hablar y pierdo el hilo
and then later that he has been very
y luego luego que ha estado muy
attentive to me he is perfectly well we are
pendiente de mí él está perfectamente
all well okay or rather
bien todos estamos bien vale o sea
simply well I have been well I feel
simplemente pues llevo pues me siento
bad because it is something that is that it is not that it is
mal porque es que es algo que es que no
a mistake you know it is a mistake it is a
es un error ya sabéis es un error es un
mistake of mine I already said that  I was going to talk about
error mío ya dije que iba hablar yo de
this, you know that in the end, as what I
esto sabéis que al final como lo
did and obviously I apologized
cometido y obviamente le pedí disculpas
to him, I also apologized to his side,
a él también pidió disculpas a su bando
of course if there are two people, the one
por supuesto si hay dos personas la
involved and that's the only ones I have to
implicada y eso para los únicos que les
apologize to, the rest, the
tengo que pedir disculpas el resto la
truth is that I don't give a damn JCE because he is who he
verdad es que me la suda jce porque es
is,
el que es
always and when someone else, I
siempre y cuando alguien más
think that's all so nothing happens
creo que es todo así que no pasa nada
but it is true that it felt terrible to me
pero sí que es verdad que me supo fatal
because of the love that I have for him, a lot, he is very
por el cariño que le tengo un montón es
good, pure, pure, people, the
muy buena puro va puro la gente la
truth is that he took it very well,
verdad que él se lo tomado muy bien está
our country is very good because it is doing
muy bien está nuestro país porque le
very well for him, in fact, I think that I
está muy bien de hecho creo que yo
was worse than him,
estuve peor que él
although it sounds strange, I was quite a bit worse than him,
aunque suene raro estuve bastante peor
but oh well, that's what happened, it was a
que él pero bueno es lo que pasó era una
story that had to be uploaded to
historia que se tenía que subir a
best friends and unfortunately, well, it was
mejores amigos y por desgracia pues se
uploaded
ha subido a
for a few seconds, which was
durante unos pequeños segundos que fue
the mistake of deleting it, well, it was uploaded
el error para borrarlo pues se ha subido
and unfortunately for the people, well, you
y desgraciadamente por la gente pues
know, there are people who are bad,
pues ya sabéis hay gente que es mala
people who are bad and I think that more than
gente que es mala y yo creo que más que
hurting him, it was
por hacerle daño ahí fue por hacerme
hurting me, not why they
daño a mí no lo por por lo cual lo han
shared it, basically, that's why I feel
compartido básicamente por eso me sabe
very bad for him, yes  at least he was very
muy mal por él si al menos él estaba muy
well and he is very eager I
bien y él está con muchísimas ganas le
wish him much success really when he
deseo muchísimo éxito realmente cuando
decides to do his weak faith that will be a huge
decida hacer su fe débil que será un
success I do not doubt it he is a great
exitazo es que no lo dudo es una gran
person and well things happen or things
persona y bueno cosas que pasan o cosas
that happen what happens is that if the person
que pasa lo que pasa que si la persona
who does it is called picking it is like
que lo hace se llama picking es como
this you know that is simply it is like that
esto ya sabes esa es simplemente es así
nothing happens we are all good
que no pasa nada estamos todos bien en
stop trying please people
dejar de intentar por favor que la gente
stop making things up we all
deje de inventarse cosas todos nos
get along very well all good the only ones who do
llevamos muy bien todos bien los únicos
n't understand anything are making up
que no se entera de nada que se inventa
things a little strange we are all
cosas un poco extrañas todos estamos
perfectly fine there is a very good vibe between
perfectamente hay muy buen rollo entre
everyone we are all friends we
todo el mundo somos todos amigos nos
all love each other very much and we are here for
queremos todos mucho y aquí estamos para
everything is worth it so please stop
todo vale así que por favor dejad de
and nobody cares about us none of us
y no nos importa a nadie a ninguno nos
care
importa
for me I always have a comparison
para mí yo siempre tengo una comparativa
and especially that you have tortillas
y sobre todo la que tengáis tortillas
you know what I mean not in tortilla
sabéis a qué me refiero no en tortilla
we started called tortilla
tenemos un empecé que se llama tortilla
snpc every time you talk to him he was only
snpc cada vez que le hablas sólo estaba
insulting valuable they upload epc that only
insultar valiosa suben epc que sólo
insults so to me all these people
insulta así que a mí toda esta gente me
remind me a lot of tortilla for me they are
recuerda mucho a tortilla para mí son
like tortillas they are npc it is that instead
como tortillas son npc es que en lugar
of saying things  good or not say anything or
de decir cosas buenas o no decir nada o
such they start foaming and bile at
tal se ponen a echar espuma y bilis por
the mouth no for me I think it's a
la boca no para mí yo creo que es una
good comparison so when you
buena comparativa así que cuando os
remember tortilla remember all
acordáis de tortilla acordaros de toda
these valuable people it's something very
esta gente valiosa es algo muy
important that you keep in mind and above
importante que tengáis en cuenta y sobre
all don't feel bad for
todo no os pongáis mal vosotros por
people who literally are not worth the
gente que es que literal no valen las
letters there are people who unfortunately I feel
letras hay gente que desgraciadamente yo
very sorry for them
lo siento muchísimo por por ellos
and especially the people who are older
y sobre todo la gente que es mayor
because it's true that there are people who are
porque sí que es cierto que hay gente
younger there are more
que es más jovencita hay más
impressionable there are people who are older than
influenciable hay gente que es mayor que
me who are dedicated to doing certain things
yo que se dedica a hacer según qué cosas
and it makes me feel sorry I say I think
y a mí me da pena digo yo creo que tiene
this lady has to lead especially I'm
que llevar esta señora sobre todo soy
very heavy because I really
muy pesada porque de verdad
really know what kind of life you have to lead
de verdad sé qué vida tenés que llevar
to be like this I mean why so much hate
para estar así o sea porque tanto odio
because because these things
porque porque estas cosas está hablando
the flower was talking about it was everyday not because you
la flor era de cotidiano no porque
care about your children deep than about
preocúpate por tus hijos profunda que
you worrying well it
por ti preocupante pues
was the way of everyday they are more
era la forma de cotidianos están más
concerned about
pendientes de la
identity [ __ ] and being concerned about the
identidad [__] y estar pendiente de la
lives of others because theirs is
vida de los demás porque la suya de
garbage you know because they are frustrated you have already
basura sabe porque están frustradas ya
explained a thousand times what the
ha explicado mil veces lo que son las
ways are  of everyday okay you have a gay
formas de cotidiano vale tenéis un gay
don't watch gay don't watch everyday on my
no ver gay no ver cotidiano en mi canal
main channel and they are people who
principal y son personas simplemente que
are simply frustrated because they don't have the
están frustradas porque no tienen ni la
black partner love life that they
pareja negra vida amorosa que les
would have liked to have or the money or the
hubiera gustado tener ni el dinero ni el
job that they would have liked to have not even
trabajo que les hubiera gustado tener ni
half of what they would have a lot to have
la mitad de que les hubiera mucho a
neither have nor are happy
tener ni tienen ni están contentas
with themselves
consigo mismo
lamentable they are people that in the end
lamentable son personas que al final
each one new in this life we touch
cada un nuevo en esta vida nos toca
had one thing or the other or whatever
tenía una cosa o la otra o lo que sea
okay but what can't be is a bad
vale pero lo que no puede ser es mala
person and hateful okay
persona y odioso vale
what happens to those people who see
lo que le pasa esas personas que vean a
girls like sara that everything that maybe
chicas como sara que todo lo que a lo
she would have liked to wish to be
mejor ella le hubiera gustado desear ser
okay pretty good body she is
vale guapa buen cuerpo lo está
succeeding has money to
triunfando tiene dinero para
buy a house every day I think not surely surely
comprarse una casa cada día yo creo no
in each of
seguramente seguramente en cada uno de
her live shows the money to buy
sus directos en el dinero para comprarse
a house most likely not and is with
una casa lo más probable no y está con
the person that she wants another
la persona que quiere que una otra
successful person no and on top of that being with
persona de éxito no y encima estar con
the person that she wants not because it is a
la persona que quiere no porque sea una
house at all or because she
casa para nada por el estilo y porque lo
has looked for it but it is that she is with that
haya buscado sino es que está con esa
person before that person is
persona antes de que esa persona sea
whoever it is do you understand me then
quien sea me entendéis entonces
girls like  sara girls like li yes
chicas como sara chicas como li sí
girls like lorena
chicas como lorena evidentemente
are obviously the typical target that those people have
son el típico objetivo que tienen esa
and damascus the truth is that they
y damasco la verdad es que se esconden
also hide from anonymity or some
además desde el anonimato o algunas se
believe that they hide from anonymity but
creen que se esconden del anonimato pero
on the internet it seems complicated to be
en internet ve complicado que sea
anonymous okay
anónimo vale
because they are really ashamed of that
porque realmente les da vergüenza esa
shame of what they do they are not
vergüenza de lo que hacen no tienen
ashamed to do it because they are
vergüenza para hacerlo porque están
behind a screen and behind a
detrás de una pantalla y detrás de un
nickname okay but in reality no no no for
mote vale pero en realidad no no no por
example the things that I say or what
ejemplo yo las cosas que yo diga o que
I think or sara okay but well above
yo opina o sara vale pero bueno sobre
all my channel is about giving my opinion and getting involved
todo yo te mi canal trata de opinar y de
in things not
mojarme en cosas no
the things that others say that I
las cosas que diga otras que opinen
whip myself with my face
látigo yo con mi cara
even with my [ __ ] name because at the
hasta con mi [__] nombre porque en su
time it did not seem to me to put a nickname on it
día no me pareció ponerme ningún apodo
seems to me that my name is an
me parece a mi nombre que un nombre
original name that is not a name I hear them
original que no es un nombre les escucho
a lot or a surname that I know a lot a lot that
mucho ni un apellido que sé mucho mucho
Javier Oliveira when he says
que javier oliveira cuando dice las
things he says them with his face he understands me
cosas las dice con su cara me entiende
but during axes and behind a nickname
pero durante ejes y detrás de un apodo
people do not invent okay and then on top of that he
un ni gente inventa vale y luego encima
takes down your twitter accounts to create
te baja cuentas de twitter a crearte
multiple anonymous twitter accounts because you
multi cuentas de twitter anónima porque
are not capable  of putting it from your
no eres capaz de ponerlo de tu cuenta
real account from your personal account what a
real desde tu cuenta personal que
shame not only to be for era of
vergüenza no solamente ser for era de
everyday but also to get along with people
cotidiano sino además llevarte con gente
from the everyday forum
del foro cotidiano
and pass things to people that there are also those that have
y pasarle cosas a la gente que también
also happened and I will
las hay también se han dado y ya os
surely tell you about it during the next year I will be
contaré seguramente durante el año que
able to tell things okay
viene ya pueda ir contando cosillas vale
but what a shame to pass things on to them in
pero qué vergüenza pasarle cosas entre
the everyday forum so
el foro cotidiano
that they attack other women
para que ataquen a otras mujeres
anyway tremendous
en fin tremendo
for your things which is another issue in the end
por tus cosas que es otro tema al final
time puts everything in its place and
el tiempo lo pone todo en su sitio y
these types of people will not happen to these
este tipo de personas no pasarán a ese
types of people to everything that is
tipo de personas a todo lo que hay
behind because things are not going
detrás pues no le están saliendo las
well for them at all apart from that and you already know that
cosas nada bien aparte y ya sabéis que
for a long time unfortunately they have been
durante mucho tiempo desgraciadamente
suffering they no longer do things but
estado sufriendo ya no haga cosas sino
psychological abuse by some
maltrato psicológico por parte de unas
ladies okay from a ladies' bunk because
señoras vale de litera de señoras porque
I have a first name and surname I know a lot of things
tengo nombre apellidos sé muchas cosas
about this lesson intermediate look notice
de esta lección intermedio mira fijaros
that we have talked about
que hemos hablado de
in the documentary about Marta del
en el documental de lo de marta del
Castillo and notice that it is left out that
castillo y fíjate que se queda en el
in 2019
tintero que en el año 2019 ya se le
telephone companies could already be asked for the data of
a las compañías telefónicas los datos de
the antennas of  telephony and with and with
las antenas de telefonía y con y con
all the data that gave such
todos los datos que daban datos tan
specific data as that on their cell phones they
específicos como que en los móviles de
could have simply requested
ellos podrían haber pedido simplemente
not the calls as the call was made
no las llamadas como se hizo la llamada
such it was made from the street it is in the
tal se hizo desde la calle está en la
call such no no no it is that it had not been necessary to
llamada tal no no no es que no había
request it so
hecho falta pedirlo así es que se podía
the entire cell phone could be tracked while
rastrear todo el teléfono móvil mientras
I am on
que estoy encendido
all the movements and all the
todos los movimientos y todos los
routes they made in Seville
recorridos que hicieron por sevilla
since Marta del Castillo's disappearance
desde la desaparición de marta del
in 2009
de el año 2009
imagine in 2021 I will pass it on you just have to
imaginaros en el año 2021 lo pasaré solo
know so that your lawyer
tienes que saber para que tu abogado
knows how to request it from the judges if you don't
sepa solicitárselo a los jueces si tú no
know there the judges don't know how to ask for it they don't
sabes ahí los jueces no saben pedirlo no
know what to ask they don't know
saben lo que tienen que pedir no saben
what to do they don't know how
lo que tienen que hacer no saben cómo
social networks work they don't know how
funcionan las redes sociales no sabe
a forum works or in other words how
cómo funciona un foro o sea cómo
Twitter works it has to be you and your
funciona twitter tienes que ser tú y tu
lawyer who know how to transmit to the
abogado el que sepa transmitirse a la
web so that they request it from the
web para que los solicite a las
companies okay well of two hundred
compañías vale pues bien de doscientos
thousand nine there was that possibility that the
mil nueve había esa posibilidad que los
judges didn't know that they were handling the case
jueces no lo sabían que llevaban el caso
Ricardo nor the lawyers of
ricardo ni el a los abogados de la
Marta's family that
familia de marta que se podía solicitar
the telephone companies could be requested of course at the
las compañías telefónicas claro en su
time  requested
momento se le solicitó a la compañía
the call data from the telephone company, hey,
telefónica los datos de la llamada oye
when did you make this call, where were you
cuando hizo esta llamada donde estaba
when you made this message, where were you?
cuando hizo este mensaje donde estaba
But today, well,
pero a día de hoy pues han salido
some specialists have come out, what have you said? But
algunos especialistas que has dicho pero
why wasn't the tracking requested? Where did they move? Why wasn't the tracking requested?
porque no se pidió el rastreo de por
The
de poder se fueron moviendo los
defendants moved after
imputados después de la desaparición de
Marta's disappearance? Well, imagine today,
marta pues imagínate hoy al día de hoy
a bitter lady who creates a
una señora amargada que se crean un
nickname and spends all day long [ __ ]
apodo y se ponen todo el [__] día
24 hours a day, who, as she said, goes out to
24 [__] horas que como ha dicho sale a
live, she charges the people she
vivir le echa la cuenta a la gente a la
hates and the ones she has to her
que odia ya la que tiene que a sus
own children, what a shame for her
propios hijos que qué vergüenza para sus
children next year or the next one or the next one
hijos años que viene o el otro o el otro
when everything comes out, what a shame for
cuando salga todo que que vergüenza para
her children, no,
sus hijos no
your father from the daily forum that the entire
que tu padre del foro cotidiano que todo
internet knows about the daily forum because it's
internet conoce el foro cotidiano porque
a forum for sick stalkers, it's
es un foro de acosadores enfermos
happened to me, maybe a
a mí me ha pasado que yo a lo mejor
good part of those who are here have been
buena parte de que están aquí han estado
subscribed here for a long time, they won't
aquí suscritas ya hace tiempo que no me
continue with the section with me, no, no, I
seguirán con la sección conmigo no no yo
know that I reported one of them, well, something happened
sé que a una la denuncie bueno pasó una
that was incredible, that I talk about  I'll
cosa que fue increíble que yo hablo a
tell you when I can put it together okay but
contaré cuando pueda montar la vale pero
incredible what he did okay I'll
increíble lo que lo que hizo vale ya os
tell you
contaré
[Music]
[Música]
anime not only did they start
anime no solamente se pusieron a
looking for me based on my
buscarme en base a mis historias de
Instagram stories that you could see a cushion behind
instagram que se veía un cojín atra en
what hotel I was in I don't know that I don't know how much
qué hotel estaba no sé que no sé cuánto
but here they were subscribed to payments
sino que aquí estaban suscritas de pagos
and maybe I was getting it but I was no longer
y a lo mejor yo cogía pero ya no
subscribed to payments and I wasn't getting it in a
suscrita de pagos y no cogía en un
live show and I made a mistake in something because
directo y me equivocaba en algo porque
the live shows you go through no that you make a mistake
los directos pasas no que te equivocas
you can post one you already the second
puedes poner un tú ya el segundo
delete it because you're wrong like the
borrarlo porque estás equivocado como la
last room with the story of this great that
pasada sala con la historia de esta gran
happened to me too
que eso me pasó también
if I posted a tweet and I made a mistake in
si yo ponía un tweet y me equivocaba en
something
algo
that I hadn't leaked I hadn't deleted
que no había filtrado no había borrado
it or something was seen in the tweet and I
lo desea o que se veía algo en el tuit y
deleted it running the seconds I already
lo borraba corriendo los segundos ya lo
had it but it could be the tweet at
tenía pero ya podía ser el tweet a la
one in the afternoon at twelve at night at
una de la tarde a las doce de la noche a
4 in the morning and live the same if I made a
las 4 a mañana y en directo igual si yo
mistake I would say something live that
me equivocaba decía algo en directo que
I missed
se me escapaba
even if I ran and deleted the live show
aunque corriera y borrara el directo
running just as it ended I had it
corriendo tal y como terminaba lo tenía
in the recorded piece
en el trozo grabado
and for that nothing there is an option  the
y para eso nada que hay una opción el
twitter stick that they follow me with
palo de twitter que me siguen con
twitter accounts where they have my
cuentas de twitter donde tienen mis
notifications activated exclusively
notificaciones activadas exclusivamente
and I asked them where it asks them when
y les pidió donde les pide cuando suena
the notification sounds you will know it captures it and
la notificación lo sabréis lo captura y
regarding the live streams
respecto a lo de los directos
the only application that there is is that it is
la única aplicación que hay es que esté
recording the live streams as they are being
grabando los directos conforme se están
broadcast that they are pending when I
emitiendo que están pendientes de cuando
do law and when I am doing
hago derecho y cuando estoy haciendo
live it is sure that they are still
directo está seguro que todavía están
following well I know
siguen bueno lo sé
incredible now we have been talking for
increíble ahora llevamos ya hablando de
more than a year it is that the day with the
más de un año es que está el día con la
room
sala
people because I have spoken with my
gente porque yo he hablado con mis
lawyers and well, they imagined what it is like to
abogados y bueno pues lo imaginaron como
catch those people I
es pillar a esa gente
told him to send a couple of
le dije mandar un par de un par de
court orders
órdenes judiciales
to a couple of companies there will
a un par de empresas
come a day when a
llegará un día donde les llegará una
complaint will arrive at their home for a bunch of crimes
querella a casa por un montón de delitos
that have been committed I am very sorry
que se han cometido lo siento mucho
one day I would have to say it I did not
algún día tendría que decirlo no lo
want to say it until now that everything arises well
quería decir hasta ahora que surge todo
look let's release everything there is a
pues mira vamos a soltarlo todo hay una
complaint that you are going to [ __ ] let's be
querella que os vais a [__] vamos que
it I have taken apart from wing I do not know
sea he cogido aparte de ala yo no sé
why this has been said I already
para qué se ha dicho esto yo ya esto lo
knew this for a while but you will see to warm up he
sabías de tiempo pero verás a calentar
said I would not have said
ha dicho yo no hubiera dicho
I am not going to let it happen but  look at
yo no voy a dejar que haya pero fíjate
you, you have to be really annoying
tú que ya hay que ser
because now we can't just give our opinion, give our
para tocarle los [__] porque ya no a
opinion, here we give our opinion, everything
opinar opinar aquí opinamos todo
to Sara and Salcedo's channels, the criticism,
a sara y canales de salcedo la crítica
but that obsession, that illness, to
pero ya esa obsesión esa enfermedad a
a stupid aura
una aura pava
that almost gives a report to a
que lo mismo le da denuncia a una
person and says in Spain
persona casi y dice en spain
that he has money to report the
que tiene dinero para denunciado al
doorman
portero
that he has money to go to the US or
que tiene dinero para ir a eeuu o
hire a lawyer in the United States or
contratar un abogado en estados unidos o
in Florida or wherever the owner of the
en florida o en donde esté la dueña del
forum is or in California wherever the [ __ ] it is
foro o en california donde [__] sea
and report the idea also
y denunciar la idea también
where the forum servers are, they
dónde están los servidores del foro
also looked for another lawyer, I mean, you have to
también buscaron otro abogado o sea es
be an idiot
que hay que ser [__]
because you think that's how it is, well,
porque te creas que hay como está pues
turn it, you created another account with a
turn it has creado otra cuenta con otro
different name, they're not going to be able to,
nombre diferente no te van a poder
dude, forced to explain, be it any
tío obligado a explicar sea cualquier
phone company knows where we've
compañía de teléfono sabe dónde hemos
been today, all [ __ ] day
estado hoy todo el [__] día
where we've been all [ __ ] day,
donde hemos estado todo el [__] día
all the trips I've made around the
todas las vueltas que haya dado por el
world in Spain today, your
mundo por españa hoy tu compañía de
phone company knows it,
teléfono lo sabe
imagine on the internet the lady who doesn't
imagínate en internet la señora que no
know, me,
sabrá a mí
everything that's in your account, on your
todo lo que haya en tu cuenta en tu
cell phone and everything  link to
móvil y todo se vincula a
numbers you have to
números
be an idiot and declare another
hay que ser [__] y declara otro
way
modo
if maybe it is a person who is
si a lo mejor es una persona que te
dedicated to
dedicas a
criticizing people because of your content
criticar a la gente porque tu contenido
because I know that they earn money you have
porque yo sé que gana dinero tienes
some benefit in return you can
algún beneficio a cambio te lo puedes
afford it but on top of that people who are here are
permitir pero encima gente que estamos
hungry
está hambre
the person who is the one who carries all this who
la persona que es la que lleva todo esto
thinks he is very smart but he is not that
que se cree muy lista pero no lo es
much I have caught three
tanto lo he cogido a tres cabezas de
scapegoats I am sorry it has touched you for
turco lo siento ha tocado por vosotros
not having been so active or having
no haber sido tan activas ni haber
committed so many crimes and a
cometido tantos delitos y se llevará una
complaint will be filed to my liking he will file a
querella a mi gusto se llevará una
complaint and let's see what happens let's see what happens let's
querella y a ver qué pasa a ver qué pasa
see who laughs and let's see what happens
a ver quién se ríe y a ver qué pasa
now okay that is the only thing I have to
ahora vale es lo único que tengo que
say about it only that it has nothing to do
decir al respecto solo que nada que ver
with twitter or fands this is a
con twitter ni con fandós esto es una
separate thing that I have like some
cosita aparte que yo tengo como unas
ladies who are crazy that literally my
señoras que están locas que literal mis
lawyers have made me lightning that because it
abogados me han hecho rayo que porque ha
came out of that merger they have been
salido de esa fusión nos llevan un mes
after these people for a month or so
detrás de estas personas o sea
basically like that speaking of other things
básicamente así hablando de cosas más
okay
pues vale
Javier computer forensics can extract
javier informático forense puede sacar
the history of exceptions that is
el historial de excepciones que queda
recorded on the computer disk I
grabado en el disco del computador yo lo
have done it in practice it can be done  all all
he hecho en práctica se puede hacer todo
seven had a lady or a
los siete tuvo una señora o una
forty-something
cuarentona
every mother has logged in once from the
toda madre se ha metido una vez desde el
device with VPN with many people who
dispositivo con vpn con mucha gente que
log in and on top of that 24 hours from all
se mete y encima 24 horas desde todos
the places you move every day at
los sitios de donde te muevas al día en
home at work around ping ping ping
tu casa en el trabajo en torno a ping
ping logged in to the forum and everything
ping ping ping metido en el foro y todo
thank you very much
muchas gracias
eating tea and now a [ __ ]
comer tea y ahora denunción de la [__]
complaint and it's not that but it also
[__] y ya no es eso sino que además
depends on what the cases are not civil he
depende lo que los casos no sea civil ha
said he wants because if it
dicho querer ya que
's a complaint it's criminal I don't think it's fair
si es querella es penal creo no se vale
but
pero
normally lawyers cost you
normalmente los abogados te cuestan en
depending on what you ask for now without sacred
función a lo que pidas ahora sin sagrada
image he's asking now each one
imagen está pidiendo ahora cada una
depends on the severity of what he's done
depende la gravedad de lo que ha hecho
precise now he's asking one
precise ahora le está pidiendo
hundred thousand from each one you can't
cien mil a cada una no te puedes
defend yourself only 20,000 or 30,000 more
defenderte solamente 20.000 o 30.000 más
then if he convicts you it's a [ __ ] ruin
luego si te condena es una [__] ruina
for the rest of your [ __ ] life for a person
para toda la [__] vida para una persona
like that for a person who has a
así para una persona que tenga un
humble job west for or whatever
trabajo humilde oeste para o lo que sea
tampa that they really tie if he declared
tampa que amarren de verdad si declaró
[Music]
[Música]
to
a